module.exports = [
    {
        question: "Which of the following is not one of the 6 paradigms of human interactions?",
        choices: ["Win-win", "No-lose", "Lose-win", "No-deal"],
        answer: "B"
    },
    {
        question: "The first habit is about taking control. In Covey's words, this means being what?",
        choices: ["Proactive", "Selfless", "Analytical", "Morally Sound"],
        answer: "A"
    },
    {
        question: "Habit three is about 'putting first things first', which of the following is a fundamental strategy of doing that?",
        choices: ["Never say never", "The customer is always right", "Learning how to say no", "Team Wellbeing"],
        answer: "C"
    },
    {
        question: "Seeking to be understood first before understanding might be an indication of what personality?",
        choices: ["Narcissism", "Lack of trust", "Daniel kruger effect", "All of the above"],
        answer: "A"
    },
    {
        question: "Habit four, 'think win win' is contrary to which popular swahili phrase?",
        choices: ["Cha mtu buda", "Ukimwaga mboga namwaga ugali", "Hatulazi Damu", "Kwenda tezi na omo"],
        answer: "B"
    },
    {
        question: "Habit six describes relationships that are 'more than sum of their parts', how else can this be described?",
        choices: ["Good vibes", "Concise Teams", "Synergy", "All of the above"],
        answer: "C"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is the opposite of psychological air?",
        choices: ["Emotional Drainage", "Psychobabble", "Synergy", "Apprehension"],
        answer: "A"
    },
    {
        question: "The phrase 'I understand what you're saying', is a good example of...?",
        choices: ["Empathetic Listening", "Sympathetic Listening", "Civil Discourse", "Larceny"],
        answer: "A"
    },
    {
        question: "The author referes to freshness both personally and professionally as...?",
        choices: ["Mind over body", "A Sharp Saw", "Renewed Vigor", "Mental Health"],
        answer: "B"
    },
    {
        question: "What human trait does begin with end in mind aim to encourage?",
        choices: ["Proactiveness", "Self awareness", "Imagination", "Foreshadowing"],
        answer: "C"
    },
    {
        question: "What behavior does the author describe as 'two heads are better than one'?",
        choices: ["Teamwork", "Discord", "Coopting", "A & C"],
        answer: "A"
    },
    {
        question: "The authors encourages leaders to keep their mistakes to themselves lest they loose the crowd.",
        choices: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "B"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is a reliable indicator of presence of synergy?",
        choices: ["Short leaves", "Happy Hour", "Easy Going", "Covering mistakes"],
        answer: "D"
    },
    {
        question: "Which habit one talks about aiming for the stars as the sure way to touch the clouds?",
        choices: ["Proactiveness", "Self awareness", "Imagination", "None of the above"],
        answer: "D"
    },
    {
        question: "Kosa si kosa, kosa aludes to which of the seven habits?",
        choices: ["Proactiveness", "Self awareness", "Think win-win", "Synergy"],
        answer: "A"
    },
    {
        question: "Effective communication leads to more productive teams because it removes ambiguity.",
        choices: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "A"
    },
    {
        question: "Lack of clarity and vision are a common impediment to success, what habit addresses this",
        choices: ["Proactiveness", "Synergy", "Planning ahead", "Teamwork"],
        answer: "C"
    },
    {
        question: "People who always think win-win might be also be termed as:",
        choices: ["Hard core", "Opportunists", "Naive", "Benevolent"],
        answer: "A"
    },
]